Orca Full Neko Silly Queen Contest
Here comes the happy show!
Team Orca and Fruit Cheever
and Nadeshiko Takamine.
We are going to decide who is the strongest fool today!
Yay!
What's up, everyone?
I'm not very happy.
There's no one stupid here.
No, but...
You're not very good at replying to all of them.
What?
Be confident.
Who is it?
What is it?
Are you saying the first one didn't happen?
Who is it?
I'm your favorite uncle.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Now that we've got that out of the way, I'd like to ask each group
I'd like to ask each group if they think this person is a moron.
What do you think of Team Orca?
What do you think of Team Killer Whale?
We don't have many stupid people.
If I had to say... If I may say so.
Then we're all in agreement now.
I kind of mispronounce things.
Like when I'm MCing.
I have a lot of words in my vocabulary.
I have a hard time getting it right.
A lot.
I see.
One hardship after another.
Oh, you know.
That's great.
One lull and another lull.
It's so unfortunate.
What are you talking about?
It's a word.
One cigarette and then another.
The clothes go away, too.
You see...
Idiots are so confident.
I don't know...
Stupid people have a mysterious confidence.
It's cool.
I don't think it's cool.
It's better not to be stupid.
Next, let's hear from Fruit Zipper.
Do you know who's in charge of idiots?
I am...
Lastly...
We sell our products to the brightest and the brightest.
I said "brilliant. I said I'm brilliant.
I'm selling myself as a brilliant person.
Mr. Shinde, I doubt that.
Yes, all of them.
And some of them are trilingual.
There's also a trilingual girl.
Yes, Aya.
Trilingual.
She can speak three languages.
But I don't understand Japanese.
Please don't do that all of a sudden.
Suddenly?
Suddenly.
Okay.
You know what?
Laughter.
(laughter)
You're an idiot!
I'm not stupid!
So there's no such thing?
I'm fine.
Are you sure? Are you sure?
I'm confident.
I'm not sure, Mr. Nakada.
I'm getting my throat fixed.
But you'll do well on the test, right?
I do.
I got a 98 in PE.
I hate it when people only get good grades in PE.It's not good to be the only one who gets good grades in PE.
Let's continue.
There are 10 Nadeshiko Takahata students.
Are you sure you're all idiots?
There are 10 of us, so we're all idiots.
I see.
But who's the only one?
But she's more like a grandmother.
I'd say she's more of a natural.
Who is it?
I'll tell you.
Surprising.
Hina-san, is that you?
Higashiyama-san?
Your ponytail is attacking me.
When I pull it out the side.
Your ponytail.
It says you're whispering to it.
Is that so?
No, I didn't think so.
That's good. Natural people don't think it's them.
That's because they're natural.
Are you like that too?
I'm pretty much just another idiot.
But you're very kind to me.
No?
Are you sure you want to be independent now?
Yes, I am.
Now then, I'd like to explain the rules.
We're going to have a general knowledge question. We're going to be asking some general knowledge questions now.
If you know the answer, please take the microphone in the center.
Please take the microphone over there and answer the question.
So it's like a quick answer.
So, please start to answer the questions.
If you understand, you can answer in the middle of the question.
If you answer in the middle of a question, you'll look really cool.
Yay!
And if you answer correctly, you win.
The last one standing is the queen of idiots. The team with the last one standing will be designated as the idiots.
We'll have a live show with three teams, and fans will come to see the show.
Fans will be coming too. I'm sure of it!
Wow, it's the idiot supporters!
Yay!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Question 1: How many prefectures are there in Japan?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
You can take it.
Can I?
If you don't take it, it'll look like you're being pushy.
Please answer correctly, Ms. Hazuki.
The 47 prefectures.
Correct.
No, it's great, but the scariest thing is that some of you didn't move at the time of the most vocal question.
You know, it's a win-win situation.
Now we're out of here, and we'll go on and on like this, taking a question and a charge, and then we'll come to the second question. Now we're out of the first question, and we're going to try to do more and more questions like this, and we're going to take a question and a charge, and then we're going to go to the second question.
The Tokyo Tower is 333 meters high.
How tall is the Tokyo Sky Tree?
634 meters.
Correct! Great!
Now, Mr. Haruno, you've fallen for it.
What a comical sight!
Very good.
What happened?
My nametag came off.
Your face is all red. Are you all right?
What is it? That's more embarrassing than having your nametag removed.
That's wonderful, Mr. Akiyama.
Did you get the general idea? This is what's left of Tokyo Tower.
The only tower taller and more representative of Japan was the Sky Tree.
Even these markings are very clever.
It's nice.
Let's go to the third question.
Horse.
In English, please.
Oh, this is...
Ayasan, it's already in English.
Spell it in English.
That's it!
Are you guys English speakers?
Spell "horse" in English.
Horse
Correct.
Excellent.
Excellent pronunciation. Great pronunciation, too.
The R's are pronounced with the tongue sticking up.
Horse
Correct.
Now let's come to the fourth question.
What is the name of this stone statue in Egypt?
Oh, here we go.
It's good.
Sakura, that's good.
Excellent.
Now what is the name of this stone statue?
Sphinx.
Correct.
It's wonderful.
Daikoku... he's been perched on the wall the whole time.
I think he's a maraion.
Let's do our best, gentlemen.
Here we go.
What's the answer to "four times three times two"?
The answer to "four times three times two" is...
There she goes, there she goes, the woman who dropped her name tag, there she goes.
Ten correct.
That's good.
This isn't math. It's arithmetic.
Arithmetic.
Your vocabulary's a little weak.
Come on, Mr. Fullchip, are you all right?
I see what you just said. I get it now.
I know what that was.
I was in the back row. I couldn't get out.
I have a legitimate excuse.
What is the current birthrate in Japan?
First births?
Twenty-three percent.
No, sir.
Twenty-three?
Oh, I see!
Two tables, three tables.